They sell online piano courses for $997.
I'm at 1.4 million a year.
I wanna get to 3.6 million.
I'm stuck at my long-form YouTube channel.
I basically rank for almost all the learned piano
for beginners to have keywords.
If I had to bet which thing
would double the business most likely,
for sure, bar none, it would be run-ins.
For sure, like I put all my money on that one.
And it's not only reach the entirety of your million,
but they also go to every other person
that's found interest in your stuff,
who's just a lurker,
which you probably have a 10 times bigger audience
of people who have watched a video
or two videos or three videos,
but just never hit the sub button.
Should I learn ads myself, hire an agency,
or hire somebody else?
First, I would just nuclear-ball it,
which is if I know that I have to do something,
then I buy everything.
So I will buy a course, I'll watch free stuff,
I'll get an agency to do it,
and my deal with agencies is to read my lead book.
I like to hire one, but I wanna learn what they're doing,
and that's the deal.
And I'll pay more if I have to do that,
because that's all I wanna do.
And then once I have that craft,
then I just bought myself money.